advadult.com 2009-08-17

# SexyADV

Welcome to the **www.sexyadv.com** website run by Ambroworks,LLC (the **"Company," "we," "us,"** or **"our"** ). The Company is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of our website (the **"Site"** ) (we refer to the Site and the services we provide as described in our Site collectively as the **"Company Features"** ). As such, we have established and implemented this privacy statement to inform visitors to the Site and users of the Company Features how we use and protect the information we collect. If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please see the section entitled **"Questions? Contact Us"** at the end of this privacy statement. This privacy statement is effective as of May 1, 2008. 

**What information does theCompany collect?**

The Company does not collect personally identifiable information unless our visitors voluntarily provide it to us. We do, however, collect certain types of information and ask for personal information in certain circumstances, such as when you set up an account. The following sections describe what type of information we collect, when we collect it and how we use it. 

**Setting up an account**

In order to use certain functionality of the Company Features, you will have to create a user account which requires you to submit certain personal information. When you register and create an account, we require you to provide us your name, postal address, telephone number, and email address. If you are buying ads we require information about how you will pay for the ads with either credit card information &ndash credit card number and billing address.. If you are publishing ads then we also ask for certain information about your web site and which method we should use to pay you, e.g. check or Epassporte or wire transfer. If a publisher is based in the USA we are required to collect certain tax ID information. Upon activating an account, you will select a password. Your email address and password will be used so you can securely access and maintain your account

**Cookies**

Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a web site can transfer to a visitor&rsquos hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many web sites use them. Cookies allow web site operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor&rsquos individual preferences. For example, by setting a cookie you would not have to enter information in the Site more than once, thereby saving time. We do not receive or record any personal information in the cookies we use. 

Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent that or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access the Company Features.

**Electronic Information**

In the course of using the Site we automatically collect information such as IP address, browser type, referrer URL and other technical data.

**Customer Service**

We provide customer service support through email and phone. In order to provide customer support, we will ask for your email address. Aside from this information, we do not ask for any personal information to provide customer support. We only use information received from customer support requests, including email addresses, for customer support services and we do not transfer or share this information with any third parties. 

**How do we use the information you provide us?**

We use your personal information such as your name, address, billing and mailing address and credit card number for billing purposes when we charge you for the use of your account. We also will use your email address or phone number to contact you when we provide customer support. 

We use your email address to inform advertisers about the performance of their ads and to inform publishers about any ads that they have sold. 

In addition, from time to time, we may also use your email address to send you information on updates to the Company Features, or if you choose to be included, to alert you to offerings from other companies that we are affiliated with. To opt in to receiving these emails, please see the section below titled **"How do you opt in?"** We will not ever sell your email address or send you offerings from companies that we are not affiliated with.

We may also provide aggregated information about our visitors to outside parties from time to time. For further details, please see the section below titled **"Does Company disclose the information it collects to outside parties?"**

We may use the information we collect to optimize our Site, for internal research, to provide information in the aggregate to advertisers about the performance of ads, and to tailor your experience through the Company Features by displaying content according to your interests and preferences, providing a faster method for you to access your account and submit information to us and allowing us to contact you, if necessary. 

**How does Company protect customer information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. User personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. Any credit card information you supply us is transmitted and protected via Secure Socket Layer technology (&ldquoSSL&rdquo) and HTTPS protocol and then stored into our databases to be accessed only as stated above. 

**Does Company disclose the information it collects from its visitors to outside parties?**

We do not currently sell, trade, or otherwise transfer outside the Company personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily provide in any account registration. This information is used to better understand how visitors use the Site, to support related transactions made on the site, and to better know our visitors and possibly tailor any specific features, promotions, or other notifications to them. However, this data, in an aggregate form without any personally identifiable information, may be provided to other parties (including advertisers) for marketing, advertising, or other uses, including assessing the effectiveness of their ads. Should you change your mind about the information you&rsquove provided to us, should you no longer wish to receive information from us, or should your information change, we have provided a way for you to correct, update or remove the personal data you gave us. For further details please see the section below titled 

**"How do you change the information we have for you?"**

In the event Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, visitors&rsquo information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Visitors will be notified via prominent notice on the Site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of information of users held by us. If as a result of the business transition, information will be used for a purpose different from that stated, or implied at the time of collection users will be given a choice consistent with our notification of changes section. 

Notwithstanding any other term of this privacy statement, we may release any personal information we obtain or collect when we believe its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Site policies, or protect ours or others&rsquo rights, property, or safety.

**How do you opt in?**

In order to opt in to receiving email notifications and updates, please access the "My Account" area of the Site and you may select the **"Please send me email updates and notifications"** option. 

**How do you change the information we have for you?**

To update, modify or delete the information that we have on file for your account, simply go to the "My Account" section of the Site, log in, and modify your details and settings as necessary. To reduce the occurrence of unauthorized access to your account information, we strongly urge you to periodically change your password. Please note that we require some personal information for billing purposes. If you wish to delete your name, telephone number, email address, billing or mailing address or credit card number, you will be required to terminate your account. 

**Third party links and co-brand relationships.**

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, we may choose various third party web sites to link to, and frame within, the Site. We also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our visitors. However, even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these linked sites, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party web sites (even if offered on or through our site) may not be received by us. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the Company Features and the links placed upon each of them and therefore request any feedback on not only the Company Features, but for sites each links to as well (including if a specific link does not work). 

**Children &rsquos Online Privacy Protection Act. **

Our Site is not intended for use by children, or any person under the age of 18. Consequently, if you are not at least 18 years of age, please do not use our Site or open an account. 

**Notification of changes.**

By visiting the Site or using the Company Features, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes within this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

**Questions? Contact us.**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or your dealings with the Company Features, please do not hesitate to contact: contact@sexyadv.com

**Terms and Conditions.**

Please also read the [Terms of Service](http://www.sexyadv.com/terms.php) establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Site and the Company Features.
